export const data = [
    {
      question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
      option1: "Modem",
      option2: "Router",
      option3: "LAN Cable",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
      option1: "Asia",
      option2: "Europe",
      option3: "North America",
      option4: "Africa",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
      option1: "Spam",
      option2: "Fake",
      option3: "Archived",
      option4: "Bin",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
      option1: "Application Software",
      option2: "Internet",
      option3: "Operating System",
      option4: "Mouse",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
      option1: "Index Page",
      option2: "Homepage",
      option3: "Sitemap",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "In a multiprogramming environment, which scheduling algorithm prioritizes short processes?",
      option1: "First-Come-First-Served",
      option2: "Shortest-Job-First",
      option3: "Priority scheduling",
      option4: " Round-robin scheduling",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the process of dividing logical memory into fixed-size blocks called?",
      option1: "Paging",
      option2: "Segmentation",
      option3: "Virtualization",
      option4: "Caching",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is a data structure that follows the Last In, First Out (LIFO) principle?",
      option1: "Queue",
      option2: "Array",
      option3: "Stack",
      option4: "set",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "In object-oriented programming, what is the concept of hiding data and methods within a class called?",
      option1: "Inheritance",
      option2: "Polymorphism",
      option3: "Encapsulation",
      option4: "Abstraction",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is a communication protocol that ensures reliable data transfer over a network?",
      option1: "TCP (Transmission Control Protocol) ",
      option2: "UDP (User Datagram Protocol)",
      option3: "HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol)",
      option4: "FTP (File Transfer Protocol)",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is a network security device that filters incoming and outgoing traffic based on a set of rules called?",
      option1: "Modem",
      option2: "Switch",
      option3: "Router",
      option4: "FireWall",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is a computer program designed to automate repetitive tasks called?",
      option1: "Database",
      option2: "Web Browser",
      option3: "Script",
      option4: "Compiler",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "In database management systems, what type of join combines data from two tables based on a matching column?",
      option1: "Outer join",
      option2: "Inner Join",
      option3: "Self Join",
      option4: "Full Join",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is a type of computer crime that involves stealing personal information for fraudulent purposes?",
      option1: "Phishing",
      option2: "Malware attack",
      option3: "Hacking",
      option4: "Service Attack",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is a computer program that can learn and improve its performance without being explicitly programmed?",
      option1: "DBMS",
      option2: "Algorithms",
      option3: "Web server",
      option4: "Machine Learning",
      ans: 4,
    }
  ];